Sewall Wright Papers 1895-1988 Mss.Ms.Coll.60
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Correspondence, 1895-1988; 13.5 Linear feet
  - American Statistical Association, 1931-1962; 15 folders (Box Series I-2)
    - Buros, Oscar K., 1947 (Box Series I-2)
    - Cox, Gertrude; Finnegan, J.K., 1945 (Box Series I-2)
    - Holtzinger, Karl J., 1934 (Box Series I-2)
    - King, W.I., 1931 (Box Series I-2)
    - Kopf, Edwin W., 1931 (Box Series I-2)
    - Mills, Frederick, 1934 (Box Series I-2)
    - Miner, John Rice, 1944 (Box Series I-2)
    - Ogburn, William F., 1931 (Box Series I-2)
    - Rice, Stuart A, 1934 (Box Series I-2)
    - Riley, Donald C., 1961-1962 (Box Series I-2)
    - Ross, Frank A., 1926-1931 (Box Series I-2)
    - Wolman, Leo, 1931 (Box Series I-2)
  - Anderson, Allan G., 1950 (Box Series I-2)
  - Anderson, Edgar, 1932-1960 (Box Series I-2)
  - Anderson, Mark (Box Series I-2)
  - Anderson, Wyatt W., 1976-80 (Box Series I-2)
  - Andervont, H.B., 1964 (Box Series I-2)
  - Andrews, Henry N., 1963 (Box Series I-2)
  - Animal Behavior Society, 1968 (Box Series I-2)
    Hirsch, Jerry
  - The Annals of the American Academy of Political and Social Science, 1931 (Box Series I-2)
    Young, Donald
  - Annals of Mathematical Statistics, 1933-34 (Box Series I-2)
    Carver, H.C.
  - Annual Review of Genetics, 1965-73 (Box Series I-2)
    Roman, Herschel
  - Annual Review of Physiology, 1943-45 (Box Series I-2)
    Luck, J, Murray; Harris, Marjorie R.; Davis, Esther
  - Appel, Fred W., 1943 -47 (Box Series I-2)
  - Archer, Joyce M., 1973 -79 (Box Series I-2)
    The Rare Varieties Cavy Club
  - Argenbright, G. F., 1923 (Box Series I-2)
  - Arrow, Kenneth J., 1974 (Box Series I-2)
  - Asbury, Ken, n.d. (Box Series I-2)
  - Ashbrook, Frank G., 1931-33 (Box Series I-2)
  - Ashby, Eric, 1933-45 (Box Series I-2)
    Australian Legation to the USSR
  - Ashman, R.B., 1968 (Box Series I-2)
  - Atwooa, Banford S., 1950 (Box Series I-2)
  - Atz, James W., 1950-51 (Box Series I-2)
  - Aunt Bess, 1952 (Box Series I-2)
  - Avadhani, K. K., 1971 (Box Series I-2)
  - Avalon Park Auto Rebuilders, 1947 (Box Series I-2)
  - Ayala, Francisco J., 1980 (Box Series I-2)
  - Babcock, E. B. (Ernest Brown), 1924-1946; 3.0 Item(s) (Box Series I-2)
    Congratulations, greetings, thanks -- National Academy of Sciences; Iltis, Hugo; Mendel, Gregor; Publication
  - Bach, Fritz H., 1980 (Box Series I-2)
  - Baggett, Samuel, 1922 (Box Series I-2)
  - Baitsell, George A., 1951-53 (Box Series I-2)
  - Bajema, Carl Jay, 1979 (Box Series I-2)
  - Baker, A. C., 1924-25 (Box Series I-2)
  - Baker, Lawrence H., 1958 (Box Series I-2)
  - Baker, William K., 1954 (Box Series I-2)
  - Balakrishnan, V., 1978 (Box Series I-3)
  - Ball, Francis M., 1963 (Box Series I-3)
  - Ballenger, E.S., 1931 (Box Series I-3)
    Lillie, F. R.
  - Ballonoff, Paul, 1973 (Box Series I-3)
  - Ballou, W.H., 1925 (Box Series I-3)
  - Baluch, H.G., 1931-35 (Box Series I-3)
  - Bancroft, T.A., 1951-62 (Box Series I-3)
  - Banta, A. M., 1942 (Box Series I-3)
  - Barigozzi, Claudio, 1951 (Box Series I-3)
  - Barrowclough, George F., 1979 (Box Series I-3)
  - Bartelmez, G. W., 1948 (Box Series I-3)
  - Bartky, Walter, 1933 (Box Series I-3)
  - Bartlett, J. W., 1937 (Box Series I-3)
  - Bartlett, M.S., 1955 (Box Series I-3)
  - Bartone, John C., 1952 (Box Series I-3)
  - Bateman, A.J., 1948-50 (Box Series I-3)
  - Bates, Ruth, 1946 (Box Series I-3)
  - Baxter, Brent, 1940 (Box Series I-3)
  - Beadle, G. W. (George Wells), 1942-1965; 24.0 Item(s) (Box Series I-3)
    California Institute of Technology -- Thomas Hunt Morgan memorial; Conferences and symposia; Conferences and symposia -- American Society of Zoologists; Congratulations, greetings, thanks -- Royal Society (Great Britain); Cytogenetics; Genetics -- Guinea pigs; Genetics -- Neurospora; Invitations; Lectures, public speaking -- University of California, Berkeley; Morgenstern, Oskar; Population genetics; Recommendations; Statistics, biostatistics, biometrics; Unpublished manuscripts, notes, etc.
  - Beale, Geoffrey, 1951-52 (Box Series I-3)
  - Beam, Alexander G., 1978 (Box Series I-3)
  - Beecher, W. J., 1951 (Box Series I-3)
  - Bell, George A., 1930-31 (Box Series I-3)
  - Belling, John, 1932-33 (Box Series I-3)
  - Benson, 1946 (Box Series I-3)
  - Bennett, Arthur L., 1978 (Box Series I-3)
  - Bennett, Richard L., 1959 (Box Series I-3)
  - Berg, Raissa, 1972-79 (Box Series I-3)
    Astaurou, Boris L.; On the dynamics of the Mutation Process in Man
  - Bernet, Frank E., 1963-69 (Box Series I-3)
  - [Bernstein, F.], 1925-26 (Box Series I-3)
  - Bernstein, Felix, 1934-43 (Box Series I-3)
  - Bernstein, Marianne E., 1952 (Box Series I-3)
  - Bernstein, Marianne Magnus, 1950-51 (Box Series I-3)
  - Bernstein, U., 1940 (Box Series I-3)
  - Berry, George, 1946 (Box Series I-3)
  - Berry, Joe, 1949 (Box Series I-3)
  - Bessey, Otto A., 1936 (Box Series I-3)
  - Bethe, Hans A., 1970 (Box Series I-3)
  - Bettini, T.M., 1952 (Box Series I-3)
  - Betts, Edwin M., 1955 (Box Series I-3)
  - Bharucha-Reid, A.T., 1955-57 (Box Series I-3)
  - Bhide, Hari S., 1931 (Box Series I-3)
  - Bigelow, Robert, 1968-73 (Box Series I-3)
  - Binet, F.E., 1959 (Box Series I-3)
  - Biological Abstracts (Box Series I-3)
    - Biological Abstracts, 1931-49 (Box Series I-3)
    - Flynn, John E., 1933-49 (Box Series I-3)
    - Hess, Walter N., 1947 (Box Series I-3)
    - Kempton, Rudolf T., 1947 (Box Series I-3)
    - Schramm, J.R., 1931 (Box Series I-3)
  - Biological Society of Washington, 1921 (Box Series I-3)
  - Biology Division, Oak Ridge National Laboratory, 1952 (Box Series I-3)
    Oak Ridge National Laboratory
  - The Biometric Society, 1949-54 (Box Series I-3)
    Bliss, C.I.
  - Biometrics (Box Series I-3)
    - Elston, Robert, 1967-70 (Box Series I-3)
    - Pollak, Edward, n. d. (Box Series I-3)
    - Sampford, M.R., 1963-68 (Box Series I-3)
    - Biometrics Bulletin, 1945 (Box Series I-3)
      Cox, Gertrude
  - Bioscience, 1967-68 (Box Series I-4)
    American Institute of Biological Sciences; Prescott, David M.
  - Birdsell, Joseph B., 1951 (Box Series I-4)
  - Bittner, John J., 1931-32 (Box Series I-4)
  - Blackwell, R. L., 1979 (Box Series I-4)
  - Blake, Charles H., 1946 (Box Series I-4)
  - Blakeslee, Albert Francis, 1936-1940; 2.0 Item(s) (Box Series I-4)
    Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory; Invitations; Laboratory techniques, equipment
  - Blalock, Hubert M., 1970 (Box Series I-4)
  - Bliss, C. I., 1933-45 (Box Series I-4)
  - Bliss, P. dt H., 1950 (Box Series I-4)
  - Bloom, O., 1948 (Box Series I-4)
  - Bloom, William, 1968-80 (Box Series I-4)
  - Blow, W.L., 1949 (Box Series I-4)
  - Began, William J., 1934 (Box Series I-4)
  - Bogart, Ralph, 1950-60 (Box Series I-4)
  - Bogen, Emil, 1931-33 (Box Series I-4)
  - Bohren, B.B., 1944-55 (Box Series I-4)
  - Bohrnstedt, George W., 1967 (Box Series I-4)
  - Bonnier, Gert, 1938-54 (Box Series I-4)
    Corrigenda: Evolution
  - Boorman, Scott, 1973 (Box Series I-4)
  - Botanical Society of America, 1952 (Box Series I-4)
    Creighton, Harriet B.
  - Bothwick, Thomas Jr., 1932 (Box Series I-4)
  - Bovbjerg, Richard, 1955 (Box Series I-4)
  - Bowman, William M., 1923 (Box Series I-4)
  - Box, Joan G., 1968 (Box Series I-4)
  - Boyd, Mossom de G., 1923 (Box Series I-4)
    Black, W. H., Esq.
  - Boyd, William C., 1941-47 (Box Series I-4)
  - Boyden, Alan, 1944-52 (Box Series I-4)
  - Boyer, Donald A., 1948-49 (Box Series I-4)
    Lysenko, Trokim
  - Boyes, J.W., 1958-60 (Box Series I-4)
  - Boyle, Edmund, 1980 (Box Series I-4)
  - Braddock, James, 1948-72 (Box Series I-4)
  - Braddock, Zora, 1949 (Box Series I-4)
    Braddock, Mrs. James
  - Bradley, Ralph A., 1960 (Box Series I-4)
  - Braum, Werner, 1945 (Box Series I-4)
  - Breeder's Gazette, 1919-21 (Box Series I-4)
  - Breland, Keller, 1957 (Box Series I-4)
  - Brewer, N.R., 1946 (Box Series I-4)
  - Briggs, Fred N., 1947 (Box Series I-4)
  - Briquet, Raul Jr., 1945-49 (Box Series I-4)
    Mating tables
  - Brink, R.A., 1924-53 (Box Series I-4)
  - British Association for the Advancement of Science, 1950 (Box Series I-4)
    Hartley, Harold
  - Brody, Samuel, 1925 (Box Series I-4)
  - Broeck, Carl Ten, 1935 (Box Series I-4)
  - Bronk, Detlev W., 1943 (Box Series I-4)
  - Brosseau, George E., 1965 (Box Series I-4)
  - Browman, Ludvig G., 1935-50 (Box Series I-4)
  - Brown, C., 1976 (Box Series I-4)
  - Brown, Clarence F.G., 1937 (Box Series I-4)
  - Brown, Harrison, 1952 (Box Series I-4)
  - Brown, Kenneth S., 1954-64 (Box Series I-4)
  - Brown, L.A., 1932 (Box Series I-4)
  - Brown, Meta S., 1959 (Box Series I-4)
  - Brown, Raymond, 1920 (Box Series I-4)
  - Brown, William L. Jr., 1967 (Box Series I-4)
  - Bruell, Jan H., 1964 (Box Series I-4)
  - Brues, Alice M., 1963 (Box Series I-4)
  - Brues, Austin M., 1948 (Box Series I-4)
  - Brunet, Peter, 1957 (Box Series I-4)
  - Bryan, W.E., 1949 (Box Series I-4)
  - Buchanan, J, William, 1932 (Box Series I-4)
  - Buchanan-Smith, A[lick] D., 1933 (Box Series I-4)
  - Buckingham, Guy E., 1943 (Box Series I-4)
  - Buoy, Paul C., 1937 (Box Series I-4)
  - Bulletin of Atomic Scientists (Box Series I-4)
    - Bulletin of Atomic Scientists, 1948 (Box Series I-4)
    - Adams, Ruth, 1954 (Box Series I-4)
    - Axel, P., 1965 (Box Series I-4)
    - Davies, T. H., 1950 (Box Series I-4)
    - Goldsmith, H. H., 1948 (Box Series I-4)
    - Maculey, Irene, 1965 (Box Series I-4)
    - Oppenheimer, J. Robert, 1948-54 (Box Series I-4)
    - Poliski, Iris, 1962 (Box Series I-4)
    - Rabinowitch, Eugene, Jr., 1952-54 (Box Series I-4)
    - Simpson, John, 1948 (Box Series I-4)
  - Bulletin of Mathematical Biophysics, 1966 (Box Series I-4)
  - Bundgaard, Jorgen, 1975 (Box Series I-4)
  - Burch, D.S., 1945 (Box Series I-4)
  - Burdette, Walter, J., 1960-62 (Box Series I-4)
  - Burdus, Russell L., 1921 (Box Series I-4)
  - Bureau of Animal Industry-Bell, G.A., 1917-19 (Box Series I-5)
    Bell, G.A.
  - Burgher, John C., 1954 (Box Series I-5)
  - Buri, Peter, 1955-56 (Box Series I-5)
  - Burke, W.H., 1956 (Box Series I-5)
  - Burkett, H. Patricia, 1963 (Box Series I-5)
  - Burks, Barbara, 1927-40 (Box Series I-5)
  - Burnet, Barrie, 1960 (Box Series I-5)
  - Burnett, Thommas, 1948 (Box Series I-5)
  - Burton, Glenn W., 1947 (Box Series I-5)
  - Busignies, H., 1967 (Box Series I-5)
    National Medal of Science
  - Butcher, Earl O., 1937 (Box Series I-5)
  - Butler, Elizabeth, 1944-47 (Box Series I-5)
  - Butler, L.B., 1954-55 (Box Series I-5)
  - Buzzati-Traverso, A., 1935-48 (Box Series I-5)
  - Bywaters, James H., 1934 (Box Series I-5)
  - Cain, Arthur James, 1950-1951; 4.0 Item(s) (Box Series I-5)
    American Museum of Natural History; Genetics -- Genetic drift; Genetics -- Snails; Population genetics; Publication -- Nature; Requests for reprints; Sheppard, Philip M.
  - Campos, Lucio Antonio de Oliveira, 1972 (Box Series I-5)
  - Cancer Research, 1961-67 (Box Series I-5)
    Shimkin, Michael B.; Rush, Harold P.
  - Capek, Milic, 1961 (Box Series I-5)
  - Carlin, C.S., 1950 (Box Series I-5)
  - Carlsberg, Laboratorium, 1975 (Box Series I-5)
  - Carlson, Olof, 1960 (Box Series I-5)
  - Carlson, William D., 1971 (Box Series I-5)
    University of Wyoming; National Academy of Science
  - Carnegie Institution of Washington, 1921-1949; 7 folders (Box Series I-5)
    Blakeslee, Albert Francis; Bush, Vannevar; Carnegie Institution of Washington; Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory; Conferences and symposia; Davenport, Charles Benedict; Demerec, Milislav; Drosophila genetics; Genetics -- Guinea pigs; Human genetics; Kaufmann, Berwind Peterson; Osborn, Frederick Henry; Physiology; Population genetics; Statistics, biostatistics, biometrics
    - Blakeslee, A. F. (Albert Francis), 1922 (Box Series I-5)
    - Bush, V. (Vannevar), 1939 (Box Series I-5)
    - Cold Spring Harbor, 1948 (Box Series I-5)
    - Davenport, C. B. (Charles B.), 1921-1924 (Box Series I-5)
    - Demerec, M. (Milislav), 1949 (Box Series I-5)
    - Kaufman, Berwind, 1949 (Box Series I-5)
    - Osborn, F. (Frederick), 1939 (Box Series I-5)
  - Carnochan, F. G., 1936 -43 (Box Series I-5)
  - Carothers, Eleanor, 1931 (Box Series I-5)
  - Carran, A.B., 1964 (Box Series I-5)
  - Carson, Hampton L., 1950 (Box Series I-5)
  - Carter, G.S., 1950-67 (Box Series I-5)
  - Carter, R.C., 1956-66 (Box Series I-5)
  - Carter, Toby C., 1953-66 (Box Series I-5)
  - Carver, H, C., 1934 (Box Series I-5)
  - Caspari, Ernst Wilhelm, 1947-1965; 3.0 Item(s) (Box Series I-5)
    History of biology, especially genetics; Publication; Sokoloff, Alexander; Tower, William L.
  - Castle, W. E. (William Ernest), 1916-1962; 28.0 Item(s) (Box Series I-5)
    Congratulations, greetings, thanks; Congratulations, greetings, thanks -- National Academy of Sciences; Genetics -- Animals; Genetics -- Guinea pigs; Genetics Society of America -- Golden Jubilee; Lectures, public speaking; Population genetics; Rabbit genetics; Rat genetics; Reed, Sheldon Clark; Statistics, biostatistics, biometrics; Travel -- Great Britain; University of Chicago
  - Catcheside, D.C., 1947-63 (Box Series I-5)
  - Cattell, Jacques, 1944 (Box Series I-5)
    Science Press
  - Cattell, J. McKeen, 1929 (Box Series I-5)
  - Cattle Breeding Course Program, 1950 (Box Series I-5)
  - Cavalli, Luigi, 1945-46 (Box Series I-5)
  - Cavalli-Sforza, Luigi L., 1979 (Box Series I-5)
  - Cecil, 1950 (Box Series I-5)
  - [Ceithaml], 1954-56 (Box Series I-5)
    Brown, Stephen
  - Celarier, Robert P., 1950 (Box Series I-5)
  - The Centennial Review of Arts and Sciences, 1956 (Box Series I-5)
  - Chaddock, W.H., 1920 (Box Series I-5)
    Miller, O. H.
  - Chai, Chen Kang, 1952-66 (Box Series I-5)
  - Chaney, Doris M., 1954 (Box Series I-5)
  - Chapman, Arthur B., 1931-53 (Box Series I-5)
  - Chapman, John A., 1951 (Box Series I-5)
  - Chapple, Eliot D., 1969 (Box Series I-5)
  - Charles, Donald R., 1935-51 (Box Series I-5)
  - Charlesworth, Brian, 1979 (Box Series I-5)
  - Chase, Herman B., 1944-72 (Box Series I-5)
  - Cheatham, Paul C., 1924 (Box Series I-5)
  - Chiang, Chin Long, 1956 (Box Series I-5)
  - Chicago Academy of Sciences, 1946 (Box Series I-5)
    Burfeind, Nat T.
  - Child, Charles Manning, 1930-53 (Box Series I-5)
  - Chin, T.C., 1947 (Box Series I-5)
  - Christensen, Lynda, 1961 (Box Series I-5)
  - The Chronicle, 1973-74 (Box Series I-5)
    Willimantic Chronicle; Leader, R. W.
  - Chung, C.S., 1978 (Box Series I-5)
  - Chute, Suzanne, 1948 (Box Series I-5)
  - Clapper, Russell B., 1947 (Box Series I-5)
  - Clark, David, 1977 (Box Series I-5)
  - Clark, Frank H., 1933 (Box Series I-5)
  - Clark, Paul F., 1945 (Box Series I-5)
  - Clark, Philip Jason, 1954 (Box Series I-5)
  - Clark, W.A., 1949-50 (Box Series I-5)
  - Clark, W.B., 1957 (Box Series I-5)
  - Clarke, L. Floyd, 1936 (Box Series I-5)
  - Clarke, Richard T., 1934-35 (Box Series I-5)
  - Clausen, Roy E., 1936 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cleland, Ralph E., 1948-50 (Box Series I-6)
    Committee on Aid to Geneticists Abroad
  - Clemens, W. A., 1933 (Box Series I-6)
  - Clifford, H.T., 1953 (Box Series I-6)
  - Clifford, Trver, 1953 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cloninger, C. Robert, 1979-80 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cobbey, Maxwell, 1947 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cochran, W. G., 1940 (Box Series I-6)
  - Coggeshall, L.T., 1949-54 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cohen, Jay, 1975 (Box Series I-6)
  - Colbert, Edwin H., 1952 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cole, Dr., 1923-24 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cole, L.J., 1920-23 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cole, R., 1938 (Box Series I-6)
  - Colernan, George H., 1937 (Box Series I-6)
  - Colin, E.C., 1934-55 (Box Series I-6)
    Auerbach, C.
  - Collias, Nicholas E., 1960 (Box Series I-6)
  - Collins, G.N., 1933-37 (Box Series I-6)
  - Collins, G.W., 1919 (Box Series I-6)
  - Collins, James S., 1957 (Box Series I-6)
  - Collins, Margaret Strickland, 1955-56 (Box Series I-6)
  - Collins, Nicholas, 1942 (Box Series I-6)
  - Columbia University, 1950 (Box Series I-6)
    Loeb, Robert F.; Hutchins, Dr.
  - Columbia University Press, 1943-47 (Box Series I-6)
  - Committee Against Racism, 1973 (Box Series I-6)
  - Compton, Karl T., 1949 (Box Series I-6)
  - Comstock, R.E., 1951-78 (Box Series I-6)
  - Conant, James B., 1947 (Box Series I-6)
  - Conference Board of Associated Research Councils-Committee on International Exchange of Persons, 1949 (Box Series I-6)
    Bowles, Gordan T.
  - Conference on Genetic Epidemiology, 1977 (Box Series I-6)
    Morton, N.E.; Chung, C. S.
  - Connecticut Accent, 1974 (Box Series I-6)
  - Connecticut Daily Campus, [1974] (Box Series I-6)
  - Connolly, K.J., 1971 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cook, Clarence, 1937 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cook, D.H., 1932 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cook, Helen, 1932 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cook, Robert C., 1932-54 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cook, S.J., 1943 (Box Series I-6)
  - Coon, Carlton S., 1969 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cooper, J.H., 1952 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cooper, Kenneth W., 1943-68 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cordeiro, Antonio R., 1963 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cornell University Press, 1975 (Box Series I-6)
  - Corner, George W., 1919-20 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cosmos Club, 1931 (Box Series I-6)
    Hazard, D. L.
  - Costello, D. P., 1954 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cotta, Wayne L., 1948 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cotterman, C. W., 1949 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cousin, G., 1947 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cowles Commisssion, 1944 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cox, Gertrude M., 1945-46 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cox, Hiden T., 1957 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cox, James F., 1951 (Box Series I-6)
  - Coyne, Jerry, 1975 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cracraft, Joel, 1980 (Box Series I-6)
  - Craft, W.A., 1931-52 (Box Series I-6)
  - Crew, F.A. E., 1939-45 (Box Series I-6)
  - Crick, Francis, 1969 (Box Series I-6)
  - Croneis, Carey, 1954 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cronquist, Arthur, 1949 (Box Series I-6)
  - Crouse, Helen U., 1944 (Box Series I-6)
  - Crow, James F., 1947-1981; 21.0 Item(s) (Box Series I-6)
    Bibliographical matters; Drosophila genetics; Genetics Society of America; House, Verl L.; Population genetics; Publication -- American Naturalist; Referee's report; Statistics, biostatistics, biometrics
  - Crump, Lee, 1953 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cuboni, E., 1965-66 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cummins, Harold, 1932 (Box Series I-6)
  - The Cunard Steamship Co. Ltd., 1919 (Box Series I-6)
  - Curnow, R. N., 1978-79 (Box Series I-6)
  - Curts, C.F., 1967 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cushing, H., 1938 (Box Series I-6)
  - da Cunha, A. Xavier, 1947 (Box Series I-6)
  - [Dahifen, Wm. H. ], 1944 (Box Series I-6)
  - Dahlberg, Gunnar, 1948 (Box Series I-6)
  - Dalton, Emmett, 1952 (Box Series I-6)
  - D'Amario, Edmund T., 1962 (Box Series I-6)
    Addison Wesley Publishing Co.
  - Danforth, C.H., 1933-49 (Box Series I-6)
  - Danielli, James F., 1963 (Box Series I-6)
    Hornung, Paul
  - Darnall, H.S., 1921 (Box Series I-6)
  - Darwin, Sir Charles, 1959 (Box Series I-6)
  - DaSef, Laura, 1935 (Box Series I-6)
  - Davenport, Chas, B., 1934 (Box Series I-6)
  - Davenport, John F., 1958 (Box Series I-6)
  - David, Mabel, 1932 (Box Series I-6)
  - Davidoff, M.D., 1942 (Box Series I-6)
  - Davidson, Frederick A., 1931-69 (Box Series I-6)
    Higgins, Elmer
  - Davies, T. H., 1951 (Box Series I-6)
  - Davis, Dwight D., 1949 (Box Series I-6)
  - Davis, H. P., 1948 (Box Series I-6)
  - Davis, Hallowell, 1954 (Box Series I-6)
  - Davis, William G., 1935 (Box Series I-6)
  - Darlington, C. D., 1945 (Box Series I-6)
  - Dawson, Mary, 1951 (Box Series I-6)
  - Dawson, Peter S., 1969 (Box Series I-6)
  - Deely, Thomas N., 1966 (Box Series I-7)
  - Deevey, Edward S. Jr., 1951 (Box Series I-7)
  - DeGraffenried, Thomas P., 1949 (Box Series I-7)
  - Delaney, Still M. (Dare-Delancey), 1953 (Box Series I-7)
  - Delbrück, M. (Max), 1942-1945; 10.0 Item(s) (Box Series I-7)
    Bacterial genetics; Bacteriophage and viral genetics; Drosophila genetics; Luria, Salvador Edward; Population genetics; Publication -- Genetics; Statistics, biostatistics, biometrics; Unpublished manuscripts, notes, etc.
  - Delfraine, Varnac, 1932 (Box Series I-7)
  - DeLury, D.B., 1953 (Box Series I-7)
  - De Magalhaes, Luiz Edmundo, 1965 (Box Series I-7)
  - Demerec, M. (Milislav), 1932-1956; 24.0 Item(s) (Box Series I-7)
    Bacteriophage and viral genetics; Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory; Conferences and symposia; Dobzhansky, Theodosius; Drosophila genetics; International Congress of Genetics; Invitations; Mohr, Otto Louis; Population genetics; Publication; Radiation genetics; Russian politics and science; Statistics, biostatistics, biometrics; Vavilov, Nikolai Ivanovich; World War II -- Norway
  - Dempster, Everett R., 1949 (Box Series I-7)
  - De Myer, William, 1961 (Box Series I-7)
  - Denham, 1956 (Box Series I-7)
  - Dennis, Earl A., 1945 (Box Series I-7)
  - Denniston, Carter, n. d. (Box Series I-7)
    Crow, James
  - Department of State, 1949 (Box Series I-7)
    Morris, Lawrence J.
  - DeRoulhac, K. W., 1945 (Box Series I-7)
  - Desborough, Sharon, 1960 (Box Series I-7)
  - Detlefsen, J.A., 1915-53 (Box Series I-7)
  - DeVine, J. F., 1925 (Box Series I-7)
  - Dewire, R.S., 1921 (Box Series I-7)
  - Dice, Lee R., 1933-51 (Box Series I-7)
  - Dick, I.D., 1946-47 (Box Series I-7)
  - Dickerson, G.E., 1950-55 (Box Series I-7)
  - Diederich, Trudie (Mrs. Paul B.), 1942 (Box Series I-7)
  - Dillard, E.U., 1970 (Box Series I-7)
  - Diller, Irene C., 1949 (Box Series I-7)
  - Dobzhansky, Theodosius, 1937-1974; 6 folders (Box Series I-7)
    Biographical and personal data; Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory; Columbia University; Conferences and symposia; Congratulations, greetings, thanks -- Presidential medal; Demerec, Milislav; Drosophila genetics; Epling, Carl; Evolution; Genetics -- Guinea pigs; Muller, Hermann Joseph; Physiology; Population genetics; Publication; Statistics, biostatistics, biometrics; Sturtevant, Alfred Henry; Teaching; Travel -- Brazil; Travel -- Invitations, arrangements; Unpublished manuscripts, notes, etc.; Wallace, Bruce; World War II -- Impact on science
  - Dochez, A.R., 1938 (Box Series I-8)
  - Domm, L.U., 1945 (Box Series I-8)
  - Donald, Hugh, 1949-50 (Box Series I-8)
  - Donaldson, Henry H., 1921-33 (Box Series I-8)
  - Dorn, Mary, 1957 (Box Series I-8)
  - Douglass, Earle L., 1931 (Box Series I-8)
  - Dover Publications, Inc., 1957 (Box Series I-8)
    Cirker, Hayward
  - Dow, Richard P., 1951 (Box Series I-8)
  - Dowden, Hutchinson, and Ross, Inc., 1975 (Box Series I-8)
  - Downey, Megan, 1960 (Box Series I-8)
  - Dresden, Arnold, 1940 (Box Series I-8)
  - Dronamraju, K.R., 1966-72 (Box Series I-8)
    Cleft palate study
  - Duck, Russell W., 1924 (Box Series I-8)
  - Ducker, G., 1974 (Box Series I-8)
  - Dufur, Theodore B., 1954 (Box Series I-8)
  - Duncan, Otis Dudley, 1965-75 (Box Series I-8)
  - Dunn, L. C. (Leslie Clarence), 1919-1971; 59.0 Item(s) (Box Series I-8)
    Jackson Laboratory
    American Philosophical Society; Biographical and personal data -- Castle, William Ernest; Conferences and symposia; Cytogenetics; Displaced German scholars; Genetics -- Cattle; Genetics -- Guinea pigs; Goldschmidt, Richard Benedict; History of biology, especially genetics; Lectures, public speaking; Mouse genetics; Muller, Hermann Joseph; National Academy of Sciences; Preservation of historical materials; Publication -- Genetics; Publication -- Journal of Heredity; Recommendations; Requests for aid in finding positions; Roscoe B. Jackson Memorial Laboratory; Statistics, biostatistics, biometrics; Stern, Curt; Travel -- Norway
  - Dunnigan, Jas. P., 1922 (Box Series I-8)
  - Durant, Stephen D., 1954 (Box Series I-8)
  - Durham, Florence, 1929-30 (Box Series I-8)
  - Eakin, Richard M., 1943-56 (Box Series I-8)
  - East, E. M. (Edward Murray), 1932-1936; 4.0 Item(s) (Box Series I-8)
    American Association for the Advancement of Science; Evolution; Laboratory techniques, equipment; Lectures, public speaking; Research support
  - Eaten, O.N., 1932-53 (Box Series I-8)